So let's talk about geopolitical hypocrisy.
I'll wait for you all to join.
You know, I'd like to, I try to think about
what are the things that make folks,
and I would say one of the biggest things
that makes folks act is feeling played, right?
So when we look at the geopolitical hypocrisy
that's taking place,
this is an example of me, you, your cousin too,
being played.
When we look at the geopolitical presence
of the United States, we have to study patterns.
Because that's how we determine the efficacy, right?
That's how we determine the legitimacy.
That's how we determine the truth.
So let's talk about the last two and a half years.
We have seen the genocide of Palestinians
for the last two and a half years.
And the United States has continuously said,
not only can we not intervene,
we're going to fund it, right?
We're going to fund it.
We can't stop it.
We can't slow it.
We can't do anything to even give aid
while it continues.
We're going to fund it.
Ukraine.
Ukraine, we cool with you.
We cool with you.
So we're going to send you stuff
to fight for yourself.
We're going to send you weapons
But we can't stop Russia.
We can't, we, you know what I mean?
Like, we can't, we can't.
So when you see Venezuela contextualized as,
well, we have to go in there
and get the bad guy out
because this is, this is harmful
to us in Venezuelans.
You know that that is disingenuous
and it is hypocritical.
And the thing about it
is that none of this is new.
What's new is y'all, myself,
and the globe being connected
and aware of it.
One person right here, YK is Mario,
said, keep your eye on Wall Street
moving into Venezuela.
That has been verbalized so clearly.
Mario is on it
because the Machado broad
who did all of this dancing
and even donated
or dedicated her Nobel Peace Prize,
which is a joke,
to DT.
She said,
what we need to do
is to bring private companies
into Venezuela
and it is gonna be
a fest
of monies.
That same chick
who thought she was about
to be put in power
is somewhere salty right now, y'all.
That man said,
there's nobody to take over.
There's nobody to take over.
I'm sorry.
She is giving that man
an entire Espanol curse
out somewhere.
But that's what she gets.
And that's what anyone gets
who trusts this person
and this administration
to ever do anything
that they don't want to do
or basically to ever do anything
for anybody else.
You understand?
That is the reality.
So when I'm seeing
so many Venezuelans
say,
well, you know,
things were bad
in the Maduro.
Let me just tell you something.
Whether your economic standing
is at the top
or the bottom,
you're gonna have to give up
your ownership
to these people.
This administration,
which is run
by the Zionists
who run
the banks
that run
the world.
And until we
as a people
really understand
how the world works,
we will never be able
to change it.
This isn't even
the actual New Year.
It is a fake New Year.
This New Year
was created
by the Romans,
by Caesar
for literally
the purpose of,
oh,
we need the troops
to be popping earlier.
That's it.
The entire globe
operates
based on a decision
made by one man
and his little
legion of people
to have war
earlier in the year.
So we have to really
actualize
the switch
now.
And that switch
is about
how we are
paying attention.
Yes,
Sonia right here
said tax day.
The first of the month
is supposed to be
tax day.
That's what it was
in the Roman era.
Calends means tax,
means payment collection.
That's where we get
the word calendar from.
So
where we are
in terms of
the hypocrisy
is
really important.
We have to
pay attention
to everything,
not just
the United States.
Now,
someone here said
they need our money
though.
Who needs
our money?
Who?
The government
or Venezuela?
Because the government
needs our money.
Which is why
we shouldn't even
be paying taxes.
Because they're
using that money
to fund
behaviors,
actions,
attacks
that cause harm
not only
to people,
but also
to entire
countries
and their
ability
to actually
exist.
I find it
wildly
discomforting
that
we are
paying taxes
all year
long
because we
don't just
pay them
to the United
States government.
We pay them
to our states.
Right?
We pay them
to our city.
all year
long
and we
cannot
account
for where
it goes.
We can't.
We have to
move beyond
the blinders
that have been
presented to us.
And when
someone says
like we
can't come
back from
this,
et cetera,
you're right.
There is a
really unfortunate
future that
is coming.
And many
people are
not realizing
because they're
in the
operation of
harm reduction
and I
understand that
but their
effort of
harm reduction
is not
to make
new ways
of protection
but to try
to hold
on to
the last
strands
of
establishment.
So,
you know,
the thing
about it,
Samantha Marie Ware,
is that it's
about money
on one level
but it's
really about
misery and
control.
That's what
it's really
about.
It's really
about wanting
the earth
to exist
in darkness,
wanting the
people to
be followers
that are
meant to
simply
just serve
a few,
wanting to
make a
race of
drones and
dead folks
and zombies
and slaves.
That's what
it's really
about.
So,
we have
so much
work to
do and
we have
to pay
attention
and that's
tiring
and exhausting.
However,
as we know
from being
forced to
run the
mile
in middle
school,
the more
you do
it,
the easier
it becomes.
You build
up
stamina.
You build
up
resistance.
You build
up
ability
and capacity.
and there
are
three main
things that
I am
bringing
with me
into this
new
colonizer
year of
2026.
One,
I am
bringing
with me
the
continued
effort
towards
a free
Palestine.
Understanding
that a
free Palestine
is representative
of a
free world.
It is
a stronghold
of Zionism
that is
required
at present
for it
to continue
to spread.
And if it
can be
thwarted,
then it
is a
huge
blow
to the
effort
of political
control
of Zionism.
Two,
I will be
bringing
with me
into
a
continued
annoyance
at
African
people
saying
that
Black
Americans
are doing
performative
Africanism,
at West
Indian
and Caribbean
people
saying
that Black
Americans
are lazy
and that
FBA
Black
Americans
calling
themselves
FBA
Black
Americans
and saying
that anybody
else
is not
Black.
All three
of those
gotta stop.
All three
of them
are nonsense,
all three
of them
are operative
behavior,
and all three
of them
are absolutely
colonizer
tactics
to shut
down
any
possible
ability
to shift
the axis
of evil.
And three,
I will
not let
go
that
Boldy
James
and
Devon
Wilson
both
owe me
money.
And I
will forever
stand on
that.
These two
niggas
still owe
me money
and I
want
my
money.
Not
because
I'm a
capitalist,
but because
I do
not like
being
played.
Which brings
us back
to the
beginning
of this
live.
What
gets you
action
oriented?
What
gets so
many folks
moving?
What
gets so
many folks
getting over
themselves to
say, you
know what,
we got to
pay more
attention?
Betrayal.
Having your
face played
in.
Yes.
So,
he and
he,
I'm bringing
all three of
them things
into this
new colonizer
year.
I will
celebrate
the actual
new year
during the
spring equinox
when warmth
comes back,
when the
plants start
a flowering,
when the
rabbits start
a birthing
babies,
when the
sun starts
feeling warm.
Yes.
Because we
got to
change.
We got
to change.
We've got
How we
interact with
the world
if we're
going to
change the
world.
Hope you
appreciated this.
Go back and
listen to it.
I'm actually
going to start
posting these
audios on
my RSSS
feed.
So, if you
have not
subscribed to
Smart, Funny,
and Black
Productions
podcast,
ooh, that
looks crazy.
If you have
not subscribed
to the Smart,
Funny, and Black
Podcast,
Smart, Funny, and
Black Productions
podcast feed,
you should do
it.
Good night.
Okay.